stocktrendinvesting.com 2011-05-01

# Privacy Policy | Stock Trend Investing - Following Simple Market Index Timing Signals

Your privacy is very important to us. At StockTrendInvesting.com we want to make your experience with us satisfying and save. On this site you can share your comments on our content, buy products and sign-up for our e-newsletter. To help you make decisions about the information you provide anywhere on this site, this notice has been provided to outline our practices.

As a general rule, StockTrendInvesting.com will not make the personal information gathered when you sign up for any of our products available to anyone outside of our company and its affiliates, except as instructed by you or where required to comply with law.

When you order a product, the personal information you provide will only be provided to outside parties if it is necessary to complete and deliver the order. Your information will never be shared or disclosed to other parties for any other reason.

If you indicate that you are interested in receiving information about a particular third party's products/services, or you opt to receive certain products or services through StockTrendInvesting, we may provide your personal information to that third party for purposes of fulfilling your request(s). With respect to service providers, StockTrendInvesting requires that all personal information be kept confidential.

We use secure hosting accounts and other security measures to protect our database and any information provided.

Any e-mail you receive from this site will contain the option to unsubscribe at the end of the e-mail. You can unsubscribe at any time.

Non-identifying information may be used to improve the site or shared with advertisers. For instance, information that is collected regarding traffic to the site or specific pages may be shared, but this will never include any identifying information.
